Trent Lott

Phone: 775-686-0558 E-mail: trenton22@gmail.com 2520 Seven Pines Ct Reno, NV 89521

OBJECTIVE

Detail Oriented Expert of Volume Licensing Order-to-Cash process with over five years of experience in World-Wide Credit Services and an additional year of Operations experience. Proven leadership and problem resolution abilities with the capability to manage a team, work autonomously, and be the strongest team player.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Accenture Reno, NV

Single Point of Contact

11/2006-11/2012

Managed a team overseeing a portfolio generating approximately \$1.5B in monthly revenue for a large business partner. Set targets on a monthly and quarterly basis that ensure consistent improvement in Year over Year and Month over Month metrics. Assist with creating and maintaining ad-hoc collections reports as needed by the business. Resolve all escalated accounts and issues in order to mitigate risk of non-collections while maintaining a positive Customer/Partner Experience for the end user, field, and business partner groups. Established self as the business expert in order-to-cash while being the contact point for individuals within partner and field organizations to provide answers for non-standard questions or situations. Work with the collections team, Team Lead, and the client's Credit Manager in order to assure that metrics and targets are met. Assess, develop, improve, and roll-out new collections processes in order to maintain optimal collections efficiency in a changing economy. Complete training and access setup for all new employees while working with all seasoned collectors in a global organization on a daily basis to provide the client with optimal business delivery.

Neutron Night-Club Reno, NV

Bartender

11/2005-11/2006

Took orders and made drinks along with additional customer service duties. Created purchase orders, received and stocked product, and tracked inventory. Was responsible for cash till, charging customers, and maintaining correct totals between multiple registers. Worked with vendors before and during special events at the establishment, the DJ's, and all other employees including security, waiters, and bartenders.

Arvato Services Reno, NV

North America SMS&P Processor

11/2004-10/2005

Processed Licensing agreements with Small to Medium-sized businesses. Handled escalated issues from customers. Tracked, met, and maintained key performance indicators for all managed queues which included Customer Care, Adjustments, Broken Documents, and Gatekeeping for NorAm. Ensured uniform understanding and adherence to operational policies, procedures, company programs. Mentored new employees and answered questions about services and programs and interacted with other departments to resolve problems, took on projects to support programs.

EDUCATION

Truckee Meadows Community College Reno, NV

Associates Degree/Graphic Communications

Expected Completion 5/2014

Working towards a Bachelor's degree in Graphic Communications.

Athens High School Athens, AL

High School diploma/General Education

May 2002

Advanced diploma received from an Alabama certified high school.

PROJECT AND CHANGE MANAGEMENT

Enterprise Days Sales Outstanding Reduction (EDSOR) Project

SME for Large Account Reseller Order-to-Cash / WWCS Representative

Oct 2008 - Jul 2009

This project was aligned with Operational Goals of improving cash flow and positively influencing Customer Partner Experience.

Impact of Project:

FY08 = \$3.6 Million Dollars saved

FY09 = \$3.8 Million Dollars saved

DSO decreased 9 days between Q1 FY10 and Q3 FY10

Revenue corrected via Credit / Rebill after 60+ days for the first time ever was 0% in Feb 2010

Revenue corrected via Credit / Rebill decreased from 26% in Jan 2009 to 12.5% in March 2010

Refund Improvement Project

WWCS Representative

Sept 2009 - Jan 2010

Reviewed and updated the refund process from start to finish in order to improve the cycle time from customer request of refund to refund payment sent to the customer

Impact of Project:

Improved average cycle time from audit to payment sent from 30 days in Oct 2009 to 12 days in Dec 2009

Breach of Agreement Automation Project

Project Manager

Dec 2011 – Jan 2012

Created internal InfoPath document for submission of data to be automatically saved on a SharePoint portal for future tracking needs.

Impact of Project:

Streamlined the breach of payment terms process resulting in a savings of 25min per instance; retaining 98% of data for future use vs. the previous 65% of data correctly maintained in the past.

REFERENCES

Matthew Ford

Microsoft Financing Operations Program Manager Microsoft Corporation (775) 722-8621 maford@microsoft.com

Heather Folmer

Business Analyst Apex Performance Solutions, LLC (775) 720-8875

Carol Mortensen

Apex Performance Solutions, LLC

Adam Schad

Microsoft Licensing, GP (775) 762-1534